JUN ZHOU

Phone:0476100764

Email: zhoujun418331@gmail.com

Profile

Highly motivated chef with more than 5 years of experience working in commercial kitchen. Served under 300 people with professional knowledge and manage skills for both functions and a la carte menu. Confident in cost management and all sections of commercial kitchen. Seeking to bring quality and delicious food to Goodstart Braddon.

Experience

Centre chef 5/2022-present

Goodstart Early Learning, Canberra, ACT

- Design and implement Roster menu.
- Communicating with director and control the budget.
- Ordering and manage stock.
- Prepare and cooking food in a timely and dealing with allergic food, special needs.
- Maintain the hygiene standard.
- Documentation include Food safety program, medical documents and kitchen records.

Chef De Partie 07/2019 – 11/2021

Jamala Wildlife Lodge, Canberra, ACT

- Manage a small team and ensure the daily operation.
- Communicating with supervisor and implement plans for cost.
- Reduce cost by 10% by analyzing high-cost items and providing solutions.
- Work as a team player and keep relationships with all staff.
- Organizing staff meeting to order priority tasks and work together within the timeframe.
- Assist team member by coaching them right skills and proper way to deal with work.
- Working under pressure while in busy season.

Chef De Partie, 10/2019 – 7/2020

Pialligo Estate, Canberra, ACT

- Preparing, cooking and presenting food in bulk
- Organizing stock and preparing order list
- Control the wastage
- Assisting head chef to develop new menu
- Following and ensuring the food hygiene
- Coaching other kitchen staff

Education

Education	
Advanced Diploma of Hospitality Management Canberra Institute of Technology	July 2019 – Dec 2019
Diploma of Hospitality Management Canberra Institute of Technology	Feb 2019 – July 2019
Certificate IV in Commercial Cookery Canberra Business and Technology College	July 2018 – Feb 2019
Certificate III in Commercial cookery Royal Gurkhas Institute of Technology	July 2017- July 2018

Bachelor's Degree of Company Management

2010-2014

DongBei University of Finance and Economics (in China)

Certificates and training:

Food safety supervisor Certificate Work with vulnerable People Card I'M ALERT Food Safety training First-aid Training course